

PRASANNA GADGIL

I.T. ANALYST

PROFILE

Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Currently working in Technical support team for L2 support team. Working on tools like (JIRA, SERVICENOW, CONFLUENCE). Worked in Telematics Automotive Domain for V2x related test bench development using CANoe Car2x. Skilled in CANoe, SQL and C#. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Engineering (BE) focused in Computer Science from Mumbai University.

OBJECTIVE

I want to work for company known for its professional approach, innovation, new technology, social commitments, value-based approach, ethics. I believe in values like respect for individual, dedication to one's work, owning up mistakes and would like to work with team having similar mindset.

CONTACT



2#502 Confole Sagami Minami, 1-24 Sonan Minami-ku, Sagamihara-shi, Japan, 252-0312



+818077991044 +919769004068



pragadgilr10@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Football, Music, Cooking, Photography

COMMUNIOCATION

English, Hindi, Marathi

EDUCATION

Don Bosco Institute Of Technology, Mumbai Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Computer Science (2012 - 2016)

Completed my engineering from Mumbai University with a CGPA of 6.7. For final year project, created a projection-based Keyboard and mouse input device using python, OpenCV for image processing in Linux operating system. Our team was selected for Annual Intercollege Final Year BE Project Competition – Trantravihar 2016.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tata Consultancy Services, Information Technology Analyst October 2020 - Present (3 months)

Currently working in L2 support team on tools like JIRA, ServiceNow. VSTS. Creating monitoring reports from server perspective for factory production on daily basis.

Tata Consultancy Services, System Engineer December 2018 - October 2020 (1 year 11 months)

Main responsibilities as IOT developer included maintenance of Manual Tool, Addition of new functionalities like data encryption decryption using AES. Development of Automation Tools for TCU functionality testing in C#, SQL, WPF.

Other responsibilities included creating POCs for acquisition of new projects. Helped in writing code module for TCU and network connectivity in using PPP protocol in phyton on Raspberry PI. Main responsibilities as on-site engineer included understanding of client requirements and proposing new software testing solutions. Understanding how V2X and 5G work and help in setting up test benches for validation of V2X services inside car.

Also supported offshore team in creating prototypes for dashboarding purpose in Azure using C# Event hubs, java, Cosmos DB and Azure log analytics.

Helped in development of daily reporting tools used by L2 support team for monitoring of malfunctions in server data.

Tata Consultancy Services, Assistant System Engineer December 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Developed service verification modules for manual functional testing tool to test TCU functionality in C#, SQL. Also developed CRUD functionalities for application to connect with SQL DB. Developed UI and basic backend interaction for Automation Testing POC for demo purpose.

Tata Consultancy Services, Assistant System Engineer Trainee December 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Developed generic modules like custom logger, report generation in Excel, PDF etc. for manual functional testing tool to test TCU functionality in C#.

SKILLS

